Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
I think you've got it backwards.
The hiding thing, I mean.
Well, that is better.
But it's a little late at this
point, And I can still see you.
Shut up, lady!
Oh, and can you tell me
how your fever's doing?
It's choking!
Keep it down, Chopper!
Your fever seems to have
gone down a little bit.
That's good.
You happy?
Hmm.
Who are you?
Yes, it's gone down several degrees.
Should be all right.
I'm the only doctor
around here. Dr. Kureha.
But you can call me Dr. Rain, okay?
Oh, then that means we're on...
Looking for how I stay so young?
No, that's not it.
Anyway, yes, you're in the
castle on the mountain.
In that case, there were two other people
who showed up here with me, weren't there?
Yeah, they're sleeping in the next room.
Very deeply.
Two real tough guys.
This is what caused your sickness.
Wow, really?
You were bitten by a
bug called the kestia.
It's a poisonous tick that thrives in
jungles with high heat and humidity.
When it bites you, it introduces
a type of bacteria into your body.
These bacteria lay dormant for
five days, causing severe pain.
It causes a high fever,
a severe infection,
myocarditis, and arteritis, not pleasant.
Given the infection's
progression in the affected area,
I'd guess you'd been infected
for about three days now.
The pain you'd been feeling
must have been terrible,
but still it would have eased up in two
more days without any treatment at all.
It would have gone away
in two days? Mm-hmm.
You wouldn't be feeling any pain
whatsoever because you'd be dead.
This particular infection is
known as the five-day disease.
I had heard that Kestia had died
out over a hundred years ago,
but I kept the antibiotic just in case.
Where did you guys come from that
you may have been exposed to this?
Were you walking around some ancient
jungle with your belly showing?
No, ridiculous.
Uh...
Does this situation sound familiar at all?
What a crazy girl you are, then.
Now, stay in bed.
The treatment for the disease
isn't completely finished yet.
Thank you so much.
I'll be fine as long
as my fever goes down.
My body will take care
of itself after that.
Well, aren't you an optimistic one?
This disease normally takes a course of
treatment ten days long
to successfully cure.
Even with medicines as
advanced as mine are,
your body will still
need at least three days?
to fully recuperate.
If you don't want to risk more suffering
and possibly death, get some rest, girl.
I can't stay that long!
We need to get Vivi home!
Back to Alabasta!
When a patient leaves this castle, it's
because she's either cured or deceased.
You aren't going anywhere, girl.
You better get used to it.
He climbed this mountain
with his bare hands.
That's almost three miles
of sheer rock to go up.
His entire body is on
the brink of frostbite.
What was he thinking dressing
like that for such a climb?
Draw some hot water and throw him into it.
This guy is bleeding a whole lot.
He has six broken ribs
and a spinal fissure.
Can I operate on him, Dr.
E?
Apparently the most critical of
our three patients is this girl.
This one's dying.
Chopper, have phenocall, cardiotonic,
and thiosaline ready for me.
She has an infection?
Yes, and the infection isn't
from anywhere on this island.
Don't worry, boy.
I'll make the bleeding kid
and the sick girl better.
You can rest easy, all right?
Those two are my friends, okay?
I figured that kid.
I'll save them, so don't worry.
Chopper, let's begin treatment.
Those two are my f-friends, okay?
I'm hungry.
So hungry.
Need meat.
A renaissance stew should
be simmered in a large pot
for three hours until all
the meat becomes tender.
Venison.
Somebody help me!
Hold on, Luffy!
Let me cook this guy up first!
Nami!
Nami, dear!
You look like you're all better!
Getting there, thanks.
Right.
One tasty venison dish for Nami coming up!
Come back!
I'm impressed.
Those guys are already up and moving.
Yeah, they are.
Can you tell me about this talking deer?
Figured you'd ask about him.
Don't run away, meat!
Don't eat it yet!
Leave me alone!
His name is Chopper.
He's just a reindeer with
a blue nose, that's all.
But normal reindeers don't talk.
If he's different from ordinary
reindeers in some way...
If he's different?
I am not food for you, okay?!
If he's different, it's just because
he ate a human-human fruit, that's all.
A human-human fruit.
A Devil Fruit, right?
That's right.
He's still a reindeer, but now
he has the abilities of a human,
like talking and walking abroad.
No! This way!
And also, he's a doctor.
I taught Chopper everything that I
know about the field of medicine.
What a shame.
Already over?
Well, that was disappointing, wasn't it?
Amazing.
Right!
Zoro, that was a good job!
Just like I told you to do!
Yeah!
Great.
Now we can go over there
and look for Dalton.
Let's go!
Thank you, sir.
Hurry! Dig everywhere!
So what's going on here?
Why are they all so worked up?
I'll explain it all to you later.
For now, let's just give them a hand.
Come on, Dalton.
Please still be alive.
You should be one of
my crew please old lady
we really need to have a doctor on board.
Luffy you did tell me
that's your name isn't
that right yeah right
that's what i said old lady.
If i were you i'd be a little
more careful of what i say.
I'm still well within my youthful 130s
thank you jeez you're a tough old head.
Are you boys really asking
me to become a pirate?
Don't be ridiculous.
That would be an incredible
waste of my precious time.
Besides, I have no interest
in life on the sea.
Those are all lame excuses.
It's about adventure, old woman.
Well, this one's a slow learner.
Didn't I just tell you
to watch what you say?
So these guys are pirates?
Wait, food, come back here! Slow down!
Get back!
That's enough of that, idiots!
In just a few minutes,
I'm going to cook you a delicious
reindeer dish you'll never forget!
I don't think so!
I'll eat you guys first
before I let that happen!
Scary fact!
I don't care about food, I
just want some peace and quiet.
Snow?
But that shouldn't be inside the castle.
It's freezing.
I'll close the door.
No, you need to stay in bed.
After all, you still have a fever.
I don't think so.
It seems like it's pretty much gone now.
I lost him, at least for now. Dr.
Ene's medicine works
quickly to reduce the fever.
But the bacteria from
the castia will still
remain inside your body
for a little while longer.
So just take your antibiotic
shot and stay in bed.
Thank you. Hmm?
You're the one who's been
taking care of me, aren't you?
You just shut up!
I don't need thanks from you
or any other low-life human!
Don't mock me!
Oh, never mind that, I'm just being silly.
No, seriously, I'm being such a fool.
He's not so good at hiding his emotions.
Everyone we found Dalton over here
what yeah fantastic we're coming.
Who's Dalton?
This is horrible I can't feel a heartbeat.
This castle is really strange.
It's freezing and filled with snow.
It's cold in here!
Not the sharpest knife in
the drawer, are you, Luffy?
Look at this.
There's snow everywhere.
And look.
All the doors to the unused
rooms are frozen shut too.
Come back here in just a moment, boys!
I said come back here!
You should rethink this idea about
asking the old hag to join our team.
A real doctor doesn't
chase her patients around
a freaky snow-filled
castle trying to kill them!
Is it true that you guys are pirates? Yes.
Really?
Real pirates? Real pirates.
So you have a flag with a skull on it?
We do.
It's on our ship.
So you're really
interested in pirates, huh?
No! Not at all! You idiot!
Shut up!
All right, all right, I get it.
Now calm down.
But one more thing.
Do you want to come with us?
You could come sail with
us out on the ocean.
Hmm?
If you did, that would
really help me out a lot.
If we had a doctor on this ship, then
I wouldn't have to stay in this place?
three more days, right?
I think you'd have a really
good time if you came.
No! That's crazy!
You realize I'm a reindeer!
I don't belong on a ship
with a bunch of humans!
I mean, just look at me.
I'm a reindeer, but I walk on two
lakes, and I talk and everything.
Animals aren't supposed to
be able to do that stuff.
Uh, I know.
But if you're trying to scare
me off, it isn't working.
But I have a blue nose.
There you are, meat!
Come here, Peter!
Come back!
Those brats sure can run, can't they?
I don't much like what you
were doing there, girl. Hmm?
Trying to tempt my reindeer away
from me without my permission.
What?
I need your permission to make
a move on a man all of a sudden?
No, I suppose you don't.
If you want to take him
away from here, go ahead.
But I must warn you, it won't
be as easy as you think.
Chopper has a scar on his heart,
a deep one my medicine can't cure.
From the moment he was born,
everyone, including his parents,
turned their backs on him.
All because he was born with a blue nose.
He was forced to walk at
the back of the group,
separated from the rest of the reindeer,
even though he was just
a helpless newborn.
Then one day he ate a Devil Fruit,
and he became even more of an
outcast than he had been before.
The other reindeer pressured
him to leave the herd.
His blue nose already made him different,
but now he wasn't like the
ordinary reindeer at all.
Still, he was lonely and wanted friends,
so he went down to a village
walking on two legs, as humans do.
Hey, what is that creature over there?
But even walking on two legs, he
didn't look anything like the humans.
And for some reason, his
nose was still blue as well.
It looks like a Yeti!
It's dangerous, I'm sure!
Get the children inside, quickly!
A gun!
Bring me a gun!
Yeah, shoot him!
Quick, before he runs
away! Get him! Shoot him!
Yeah, I got him!
He didn't know what was wrong.
He couldn't understand why they reacted to
his appearance with so
much fear and anger.
Stay away, monster!
He'd gone to the village seeking friends,
but they called him a
monster and drove him away.
He was no longer a reindeer,
but he wasn't a human either.
He was something in between.
And so he lived alone after that,
caught between two worlds
that wouldn't accept him.
Now that you've heard his story, do you
think you can heal the scar on his heart?
Luffy, check out the door
at the front entrance.
It's wide open. Huh?
No wonder it's so cold in here.
Anyway, let's close it.
With it open like that,
there's not much difference between
inside and outside the castle.
Hey, stop it!
Don't touch that door, get away!
Never mind him, let's close it.
Or we're gonna freeze to death.
That's a good point.
Stop!
Did you guys hear what I said?
Get back!
What is with this guy?
What the hell is he so angry about?
Hey, come over here a second.
Huh?
Look up there.
It's a bunch of baby snowbirds.
See, if we closed the door, they'd fall.
So that's the reason
they're leaving it open.
It's freezing!
Hold up a sec. Yeah?
That weird reindeer guy.
Wasn't he speaking earlier?
Now that you mention it, I remember
him walking on two legs, too.
He's a monster!
Okay, let's get this straight?
He walks upright and talks.
But not human.
Has fur. He's little.
And becomes big.
Clearly a monster.
What a cool guy.
I bet he's really interesting.
hey, wait!
I know he should join us!
I'll do anything as
long as you are with me.
I've grown stronger having you by my side.
We've started on an everlasting ride.
I'm invincible when your love is near.
When I'm with you I have no fear.
Let's see how far we can make this go!
The world is ours.
You're just right, I know!
I see it shine.
In the distance, glistening like water.
When the sun rises in the dark.